[Music]
hello and thank you for joining us for
another product review from Sharp's
Shooting Supply my name is Tyler sharp
let's dive in so today we have the betta
FS this particular pistol is chambered
in 9mm and it has been the military
sidearm of choice for over three decades
so it had a pretty good run with the
military contracts
and then of course it was replaced by
the Glock and then the Sig and who knows
where it'll go
next this particular firum does feature
a 4.9 in Barrel so almost a 5in barrel
and a 15 + 1 capacity so plenty plenty
of capacity packed in this large frame
it does feature the three dot sight
picture and it is a dual action and a
single action pistol so you can get it
cocked back and have it as a single
action or you can leave the hammer down
and it is in Dual Action
mode the uh firearm features and open
slide designs you can see the barrel for
almost the full length of the barrel it
uh helps shave off some weight and
reduce uh reduce some recoil but it does
give you an opportunity to accidentally
burn yourself with the with a hot Barrel
but uh there's no reason you should be
holding on up there anyway it does
feature an ambid exous
safety and the mag release can be
ambidextrious as
well the Brea 92 design is an extremely
reliable handgun like I said it was the
military firearm of choice for over
three decades so it had a had a pretty
good
run the uh the safety is actually kind
of a neat feature on it so you can carry
it with the chamber
loaded with the built-in decocker and
now your Hammer's down
that does turn it into a safe
firearm and then when you obviously
disengage the safety it re-engages the
firing
pin there is no accessory rail on this
thing which is kind of surprising but
the M9 A1 and the M9 A3 both had put
accessory rails on there um you may may
recognize this handgun from several
several movies uh Die Hard lethal
Weapons 1 through four the boond Saint
which is a personal favorite and the
Matrix all use this handgun along with
numerous others there are tons and tons
of holster options for the Brea 92 since
it's been around
forever um the 92 is made in America I
don't know if it's going to show up
there in the camera but it is made in
America it comes with an excellent
warranty and it would make an excellent
uh home defense or truck gun due to its
weight being 33.3 o empty it is a little
bit on the heavier side for a concealed
carry option so let's check out what's
in the
box so it does come with an extra 15
plus1
magazine and it comes with a gun lock
and I believe yep there's the owner's
manual youth handgun safety notice we
have to put in so not a whole lot of
accessories but it does come with the
extra mag and uh that's that's about all
you need to get going on
it all in all BR a 90 2fs is an
excellent choice super reliable it's
going to do whatever you need it to do
and last a really long time doing it um
like I said little heavy on the
concealed carry side but great for the
home defense or a truck gun but uh feels
excellent in the
hand nice relatively thin thin grips put
on
here great choice swing by the shop
check it out um we appreciate you
swinging by for this one and we will
catch you on the next review